<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>e-Magazine</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/</link>
        <description>Recent content on e-Magazine</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Bhajan Hall with Clay Art</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/clay-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/clay-art/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_2.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Bhajan Hall with Clay Art" /&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This art was inspired by the weekly bhajans in our Sai centre. Small toy human sculptures were portrayed as devotees in a bhajan hall. Some traditional Indian musical instruments were sculptured as well. Small details were added as decorations. Swami’s portrait was placed in the  middle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;Gallery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_1.jpg&#34; data-size=&#34;2976x3968&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_1_huf56738272a27b4403c8cefd655b33fef_2774526_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, ./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_1_huf56738272a27b4403c8cefd655b33fef_2774526_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_1.jpg&#34; width=&#34;2976&#34; height=&#34;3968&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_2.jpg&#34; data-size=&#34;3968x2976&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_2_hu09b3f5d9190160b237ecbe30b01661e8_3079346_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, ./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_2_hu09b3f5d9190160b237ecbe30b01661e8_3079346_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_2.jpg&#34; width=&#34;3968&#34; height=&#34;2976&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_3.jpg&#34; data-size=&#34;3968x2976&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_3_hu560de1672f5980aa587ffdaab08cf811_3293009_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, ./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_3_hu560de1672f5980aa587ffdaab08cf811_3293009_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_3.jpg&#34; width=&#34;3968&#34; height=&#34;2976&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_4.jpg&#34; data-size=&#34;3968x2976&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_4_hu3302c03f0a3487be0e9913542946baf1_3436770_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, ./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_4_hu3302c03f0a3487be0e9913542946baf1_3436770_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_4.jpg&#34; width=&#34;3968&#34; height=&#34;2976&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_5.jpg&#34; data-size=&#34;3968x2976&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_5_hu39bf300c2c8a744ed84e15e8d11e6dfc_3254926_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, ./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_5_hu39bf300c2c8a744ed84e15e8d11e6dfc_3254926_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/clay-art/img_santhossh_nagarajah_5.jpg&#34; width=&#34;3968&#34; height=&#34;2976&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>God names</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/god-names/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/god-names/</guid>
        <description>
&lt;div style=&#34;margin:auto; display:flex; flex-direction:column; height:500px; max-width:500px&#34;&gt;
    &lt;iframe border=&#34;0&#34; src=&#34;https://crosswordlabs.com/embed/test-13049&#34; style=&#34;flex:1; width:100%; padding:5px 0px 0 5px; border:3px solid black; &#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
    &lt;a target=&#34;_blank&#34; style=&#34;align-self:center; font-size:12px; color:black; padding-top:10px; text-decoration:none;text-align:center&#34; href=&#34;https://crosswordlabs.com&#34;&gt;Crossword Puzzle Maker&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
div.quote
{
    font-style: italic; 
    text-align:center;
    margin-top: auto;
    margin-bottom: auto;
    margin-left: 2em;
    margin-right: 2em;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Thank You Sai</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/thank-you-sai/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/thank-you-sai/</guid>
        <description>
&lt;div class=&#34;quote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am blessed &lt;br /&gt;
With your love that makes me whole &lt;br /&gt;
Your love that never takes a toll. &lt;br /&gt;
No pen can ever explain the divine love, &lt;br /&gt;
The feeling I am trying to explain &lt;br /&gt;
Yet all creations cannot seem to stop talking about it. &lt;br /&gt;
You taught us love &lt;br /&gt;
You showered us with love, &lt;br /&gt;
I learned that love, &lt;br /&gt;
I showed that love. &lt;br /&gt;
&#34;All things are beautiful seen through the eyes of love&#34; you said,  &lt;br /&gt;
That&#39;s when I knew I was beautiful. &lt;br /&gt;
&#34;Love is the property of God&#34; you said, &lt;br /&gt;
That’s when I knew I was investing. &lt;br /&gt;
&#34;When you have ego, I-go&#34; you said, &lt;br /&gt;
That&#39;s when I let ego go. &lt;br /&gt;
Dearest Sai, &lt;br /&gt;
Bless me, &lt;br /&gt;
To give the same love that never takes a toll.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
div.quote
{
    font-style: italic; 
    text-align:center;
    margin-top: auto;
    margin-bottom: auto;
    margin-left: 2em;
    margin-right: 2em;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Why fear when I am here?</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/quote/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/quote/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/quote/img_shashmeetha_chandran_1.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Why fear when I am here?" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagawan says, &amp;ldquo;Why fear when I am here&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;Fear&amp;rdquo; means fear of anything, imaginary or real, danger, disaster, or death. &amp;ldquo;When&amp;rdquo; means anytime, or all the time. &amp;ldquo;I am here&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;I am everywhere, I AM IN YOU and not outside you, not separate from you, wherever I am;  in Prashanthi Nilayam, Brindavan or anywhere else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, we have no reason to fear as we have the Lord in our midst and have Him placed in our hearts. All we need to do is LOVE HIM dearly. We belong to Bhagawan, we are special indeed. We are one big, sweet, loving SAI family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;Gallery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/quote/img_shashmeetha_chandran_1.jpg&#34; data-size=&#34;4032x3024&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/quote/img_shashmeetha_chandran_1_hu42479eccbabc8a3a611a2498613da7c9_6681337_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, ./p/quote/img_shashmeetha_chandran_1_hu42479eccbabc8a3a611a2498613da7c9_6681337_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/quote/img_shashmeetha_chandran_1.jpg&#34; width=&#34;4032&#34; height=&#34;3024&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;references&#34;&gt;References&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.srisathyasai.org/&#34;&gt;https://www.srisathyasai.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Bhajans &amp; Discipline</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/bhajans-and-discipline/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/bhajans-and-discipline/</guid>
        <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bhajan is not merely an activity done for fun. Yes, it is a lot of fun to sing and be involved in bhajans, but at the same time it is a form of sadhana, a spiritual practice and even a form of Seva as the duty of a bhajan singer is to invoke devotion in oneself and others. Therefore, having said that, this means that discipline forms an integral part of the responsibility of a bhajan singer. Furthermore, Swami Himself has emphasised on the importance of discipline in every walk of life be it education, spirituality or service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sai bhajans is a group sadhana as it is not only the lead singer who is involved in the sadhana but everyone singing chorus, the instrumentalist and even the technical (audio/video) sevadals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swami has a beautiful way of playing with words. Once during a Trayee session with the students, Swami said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;quote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&#34;If you want to be called a boy; you should have behaviour; &lt;br /&gt;
If you want to be called a man; you should have manners; &lt;br /&gt;
And if you want to be called a devotee; you should have &lt;span style=&#34;font-weight:bold;&#34;&gt;DISCIPLINE&lt;/span&#34;&gt;.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
div.quote
{
    font-style: italic; 
    text-align:center;
    margin-top: auto;
    margin-bottom: auto;
    margin-left: 2em;
    margin-right: 2em;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, Swami does not say to be a devotee we need devotion. He said discipline defines a Sai devotee. Swami has said that devotion is like a river. So long it flows between 2 banks referred to as &lt;strong&gt;Duty&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Devotion&lt;/strong&gt;, it will reach the ocean. However, the moment this river of devotion breaches these 2 banks, the same river becomes Destruction. The following are some of the points that come to my mind based on the various talks and sharing sessions from Swami’s students who are Prasanthi Mandir Bhajan singers on the aspects of discipline that are important for a Sai Bhajan singer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sing and participate during every bhajan in a bhajan session.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A lead singer and every chorus singer should participate (sing and clap) fully in every bhajan during a bhajan session. The lead singer should not only sing their bhajan and then not sing during the other bhajans sung in the session.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Punctuality is a key requirement for bhajan singers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All bhajans singers, instrumentalist and technical sevadals should be ready in advance for bhajans. There should be 10-15 minutes of silence and absolute peace before the bhajan starts to help us prepare our minds and hearts to imbibe the divine energy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Restriction of movement during bhajans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All bhajan singers and instrumentalists should minimize movements during bhajans. There should be no unnecessary movements during bhajans. This is to avoid any sort of distraction to others in the session. Swami wants us to still our mind and body during bhajans. Only when we can still our body, can we expect our mind to be still. In fact, this also applied to all chorus singers and all members that are part of a bhajan session. Everyone should be part of the bhajan session and be still in mind and body, they should not be engaged in other activities during the bhajan session.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No talking during bhajans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unless there is a real need to discuss an urgent matter regarding the bhajan session (such as shruthi, mic issues, etc) there should be no talking or chatting during bhajan sessions. This again applies predominantly for the lead bhajan singers and instrumentalists, but it is also applicable to all chorus singers and members of the bhajan session.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Involvement in the organisation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every bhajan singer should also take on the duty and responsibility to be involved in various other aspects of service and spiritual practice in the organisation/Sai centre. A bhajan singer should make an effort to engage in other activities such as service, education, ladies and youth activities to set a good example of practicing Swami’s values and principles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Self- study and self-audit about bhajan singing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All bhajan singers should spend time and take the effort to read and listen to various materials regarding bhajans. We should listen to discourses from Swami regarding bhajans, listen to talks and satsanghs by the members of the Prasanthi Bhajan Group. This will help in improving the technical and devotional aspect of singing bhajans. Lastly, self-audit is also an extremely important aspect for bhajan singers. All bhajan singers, especially lead bhajan singers should have the humility to reflect on areas of improvement and work on bettering ourselves to ensure we are able to offer our best to Swami through bhajans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;quote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&#34;Devotional singing (bhajan) must become an unbroken stream of bliss on your tongues and in your hearts; &lt;br /&gt;
It must confer on you the uninterrupted awareness of soham, of the unity of I and He. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight:bold;&#34;&gt;(Sathya Sai Speaks IX, 41-42)&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight:bold;&#34;&gt;.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
div.quote
{
    font-style: italic; 
    text-align:center;
    margin-top: auto;
    margin-bottom: auto;
    margin-left: 2em;
    margin-right: 2em;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;references&#34;&gt;References&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link for points included in the content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kyq98iyWHlg&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kyq98iyWHlg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link for the quote cited in the article.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sathyasai.org/devotion/songs/songs.html&#34;&gt;https://www.sathyasai.org/devotion/songs/songs.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Devotion Begins With Love</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/devotion_begins_with_love/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/devotion_begins_with_love/</guid>
        <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both the above songs are dedicated to Swamiji to show my gratitude and love towards Him. The first song is known as &amp;ldquo;Ragupatthi Ragava Raja Ram&amp;rdquo;  which talks about Lord Rama and His selfless love to people around him. I have dedicated this song to Swamiji as I personally feel both of them have the same characteristics. I have read many stories about Swamiji and realized His selfless love towards His devotee around Him. He takes many different forms to help those who have surrendered to him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whereas, the second song is known as “Ra Ra Venugopala”. This song is to invite Swamiji into my life to guide me on following the righteous path to succeed in my life. Besides, I do take this opportunity to express my gratitude towards Swamiji who created this opportunity for me to participate in His 95th birthday event and demonstrate my musical talent. Thank you so much Swamiji.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been learning veenai since 2014. My first guru was Master Kabil Raj from KVSMA institute and I continued my learning with Kalamamani Sri Padmini from Sri Padmini Vidyalaya Institute from 2016 onwards. Teacher Padmini has taught me many different songs both on veenai and vocally. Thank you to my teacher for guiding me on this video. The reason for me to pursue my musical talent is my mom. My mom knows to play veenai too and she has taught me some devotional songs when I was 10 years old.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During rehearsals and recording sessions I have been facing many troubles and obstacles. Despite those problems Swamiji’s love and blessing encouraged me to complete the recording successfully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ragupatthi-ragava-raja-ram&#34;&gt;Ragupatthi Ragava Raja Ram&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/aRmtpqKUXlE&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ra-ra-venugopala&#34;&gt;Ra Ra Venugopala&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/qJDxG4MOsME&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Gayatri Mantra</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/gayatri_mantra/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/gayatri_mantra/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/gayatri_mantra/img_ambekadevi_rajathurai_1.JPG" alt="Featured image of post Gayatri Mantra" /&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gayatri has 3 important aspects: Gayatri, Savitri and Saraswathi. What are these three? What do they signify?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 1st Gayatri – Gaya means limbs of the body, the senses of the body. Gayatri means that which will take care of the effective functioning and well being of the body and senses. Gayatri means that the well-being of the body will be taken care of. Health is guaranteed. It is very important to have a sound mind in a sound body. It begins with the body.  Any pursuit of learning in life begins with the body. This body is made of five elements.  Swami speaks of this body as materialisation. Materialisation is in one sense composed of five elements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 2nd aspect – Savitri stands for life principle. It is not good enough to have only a good body. The body works only because of the life principle. Life is a gift of God.  With money we can buy medicine, the aspect that is Savitri. Gayatri is the body – materialisation. Savitri is life – Swami calls it vibration, meaning the body has limbs but there should be vibration to make it work or move.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 3rd aspect is Saraswathi – is the faculty of speech of words. It is emphasised that everything that is spoken should be the truth.  This truth is not ordinary or scientific truth. It is unchangeable, eternal and permanent, it is beyond time and space. Such a kind of truth is verbally spoken and is called the aspect of Saraswathi. Saraswathi is the source.  The truth is the source. The unknowable (beyond the limits of human experience or understanding), the unchangeable, the permanent, the eternal truth.  This is called radiation according to Swami. So, radiation is the source.  It is a thermal power station. It is the one out of which everything originates. So the central source of activity is the eternal truth. Saraswathi – radiation. This radiation at the operational level is the vibration – Savitri. This vibration which enters into our body makes our senses and limbs operate. So radiation leads to vibration and this vibration will make the body function effectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The body – materialisation – Gayatri (Bhur)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The life – vibration – Savitri (Bhuvah)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The truth – radiation – Saraswathi (Suwaha)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;Gallery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/gayatri_mantra/img_ambekadevi_rajathurai_1.JPG&#34; data-size=&#34;1023x957&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/gayatri_mantra/img_ambekadevi_rajathurai_1_hu6e8bd413496e0fb645c39472a2d4ede6_322474_480x0_resize_q75_box.JPG 480w, ./p/gayatri_mantra/img_ambekadevi_rajathurai_1_hu6e8bd413496e0fb645c39472a2d4ede6_322474_1024x0_resize_q75_box.JPG 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/gayatri_mantra/img_ambekadevi_rajathurai_1.JPG&#34; width=&#34;1023&#34; height=&#34;957&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>My Parthi Experience</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/my-parthi-experience/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/my-parthi-experience/</guid>
        <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My journey with Swami started when I was 7 years old. My neighbour who was also my tuition teacher at that time had  introduced Swami to me. At that time, I was too young to realise His guidance and was just fascinated hearing a lot of stories about Puttaparthi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How it will be?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After over 40 years, finally the day came on 24th Jan 2020, Friday, when I attended my first evening Bhajan in Prasanthi Nilayam, Puttaparthi. I was mesmerised.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To this day, the experience is unexplainable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sai Kulwant Hall was unforgettable, the taste of the coffee made from Gokulam milk is still lingering in my mouth, early morning 4am Suprabhatam, 5am Nagarasangkeerthanam was a bliss, Gayathri Amman temple was so inviting and the list goes on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Experience in Sai Kulwant Hall was totally divine, tears rolled down my eyes just by listening to the bhajans. The vibes cannot be described, only felt. You have to be there to feel &amp;ldquo;Swami&amp;rdquo;. I was there during Chinese New Year celebration. There were many  Chinese devotees and the Covid pandemic had started in Wuhan but I did not feel any fear. Why fear when I am Here, I felt as though Swami was whispering to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every little thing there is very much cherished in my journey knowing Swami.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My humble pranams to dear Swami.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;Gallery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_1.jpeg&#34; data-size=&#34;1024x768&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_1_huccd797bdd23d39481c0a7d0a89ced539_105582_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, ./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_1_huccd797bdd23d39481c0a7d0a89ced539_105582_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_1.jpeg&#34; width=&#34;1024&#34; height=&#34;768&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_2.jpeg&#34; data-size=&#34;1024x768&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_2_hu04d913798dfe7b3e023d2f67c5ea5e99_93086_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, ./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_2_hu04d913798dfe7b3e023d2f67c5ea5e99_93086_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_2.jpeg&#34; width=&#34;1024&#34; height=&#34;768&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_3.jpeg&#34; data-size=&#34;1024x768&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_3_hu4d7068492b2411807e819ea9b270e9b1_103027_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, ./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_3_hu4d7068492b2411807e819ea9b270e9b1_103027_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_3.jpeg&#34; width=&#34;1024&#34; height=&#34;768&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_4.jpeg&#34; data-size=&#34;768x1024&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_4_huf444fe01a0319ae98dd4fb93926116c0_145840_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, ./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_4_huf444fe01a0319ae98dd4fb93926116c0_145840_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_4.jpeg&#34; width=&#34;768&#34; height=&#34;1024&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_5.jpeg&#34; data-size=&#34;1024x768&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_5_hu672a92d598c0b49e16a8ee5661fe643c_93289_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 480w, ./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_5_hu672a92d598c0b49e16a8ee5661fe643c_93289_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpeg 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/my-parthi-experience/img_jegatheswary_subramaniam_5.jpeg&#34; width=&#34;1024&#34; height=&#34;768&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Painting with Calligraphy Art</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/calligraphy-painting/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/calligraphy-painting/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/calligraphy-painting/img_darsina_nagarajah_1.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Painting with Calligraphy Art" /&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The background painting was inspired by pastel blue and pink aesthetics. A 95th birthday wish to Baba was lettered in calligraphic font. Some of Swami’s incredible quotes were written as well. Some details and decorations were added too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;Gallery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/calligraphy-painting/img_darsina_nagarajah_1.jpg&#34; data-size=&#34;744x992&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/calligraphy-painting/img_darsina_nagarajah_1_huc68d129a7a0c9deee9d8637a9eb12082_66704_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, ./p/calligraphy-painting/img_darsina_nagarajah_1_huc68d129a7a0c9deee9d8637a9eb12082_66704_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/calligraphy-painting/img_darsina_nagarajah_1.jpg&#34; width=&#34;744&#34; height=&#34;992&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/calligraphy-painting/img_darsina_nagarajah_2.jpg&#34; data-size=&#34;744x992&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/calligraphy-painting/img_darsina_nagarajah_2_hu343a007626208bc2de6b7b532b3d81f1_82072_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, ./p/calligraphy-painting/img_darsina_nagarajah_2_hu343a007626208bc2de6b7b532b3d81f1_82072_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/calligraphy-painting/img_darsina_nagarajah_2.jpg&#34; width=&#34;744&#34; height=&#34;992&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;references&#34;&gt;References&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/9RwKGTMFhbo&#34;&gt;https://youtu.be/9RwKGTMFhbo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Divine Lullaby</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/the-divine-lullaby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/the-divine-lullaby/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/the-divine-lullaby/markandeya.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Divine Lullaby" /&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The story of Queen Madālasā is in Chapters 25-30 of the &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://practicalphilosophy.org.au/extras/mada-lasa/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Mārkaṇḍeya Purāṇa&lt;/a&gt;. The Mārkaṇḍeya is one of the eighteen ‘great Purāṇas’ (Mahāpurāṇas) relating to Brahmā, said to have been narrated by the Riṛṣi Mārkaṇḍeya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this mythological tale, Queen Madālasā&amp;rsquo;s newborn child was named by the King. Upon hearing the name given by the King, the baby started to cry out loud. Madālasā sings this beautiful lullaby to pacify the child.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-divine-lullaby&#34;&gt;The Divine Lullaby&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/uDd3iupKUyI&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;translation&#34;&gt;Translation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Meaning&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Why are you crying?&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;You are pure&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The name you have acquired is not yours, merely a mind-created fiction applied to you&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The body is not you, nor are you of it&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The Lord of the universe doesn&amp;rsquo;t cry either!&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;This sound is an illusion attributed to you&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The qualities imagined as yours are inherent in all the senses&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The insignificant elements within the man acquire the condition of growth through the addition of food, water and drink&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;It is not a growth or diminution of You&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Within the body shell&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;You remain constant&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Do not become confounded by this body which has been fastened upon you&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Father, Son, Mother, Wife, Mine, Not Mine&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Do not assign much significance to what is only an aggregation of elements&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The deluded man thinks pains alleviate pain&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The deluded man thinks enjoyment of pleasures gives happiness&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The intelligent man whose mind is free from confusion knows pleasures and sorrows to be alike&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The carriage goes upon the earth, the body is seated in the carriage&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The Self resides within the body&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The deluded Jiva thinks &amp;ldquo;I am this body&amp;rdquo;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The Self has no attachement to His carriage&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Foolish is such ignorance!&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Life Story Of Baba</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/swami-life-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/swami-life-story/</guid>
        <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I compiled an article about Swami&amp;rsquo;s Life story. I got the information to do the article in a few books and through internet search Google. This message is very important for me because so many people don&amp;rsquo;t know about the life story of Swami so I wanted everyone to know the story of Swami.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;November 23, 1926, is a red-lettered day in the history of mankind. On that day was born in the obscure village of Puttaparthi, a charming baby boy in the Ratnakara family. None realised then, and indeed for a long time thereafter, that Divinity had incarnated in human form as Ratnakara Venkata Satyanarayana Raju, grandson of Mr. Kondama Raju, and son of Pedda Venkama Raju and Easwaramma. In the Sathya Sai Incarnation, the Lord chose the Ratnakara family on account of the purity, piety, and the devotion of its members. Prior to the incarnation, Pedda Venkama Raju and Easwaramma had been blessed with one son and two daughters, Seshama Raju, Venkamma, and Parvathamma, in that order. Some years passed and Mother Easwaramma longed for another son. She observed all the prescribed austerities, and soon her prayers were answered - she was to become a mother again. Even before its birth, Easwaramma knew that the child to be born would be unusual. There was a definite reason for such a belief. Sometime prior to the birth of this new boy, Lakshmamma, the mother-in-law was engaged in the worship of Lord Sathyanarayana. The Lord then appeared in her dream and blessed her, indicating that He would be born in her family. Promptly, Lakshmamma alerted Easwaramma that the latter might have strange experiences, but ought not to worry about them. Shortly thereafter, Easwaramma had precisely one such experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One day as she was drawing water from the well, Easwaramma was startled by the sight of a big blue ball of light. The ball came directly towards her and entered her; Easwaramma fainted and fell. The Lord had entered her womb for the mandatory stay prior to physical birth as Sathyanarayana Raju. Thus, the Lord was not begotten, but immaculately conceived, even as His Son (Jesus) had been, two thousand years ago. Sathya was born in the early hours of November 23, 1926. There were a number of unusual incidents accompanying His birth, as also in His childhood (as in the case of Lord Krishna). Though they all gave strong hints of His Divinity, few realised until much later that Sathya was the Lord Himself. But all unfailingly recognised that Sathya was most unusual, extraordinarily intelligent, precocious, and above all, always full of Love and compassion. In Primary School, Sathya helped His classmates in diverse ways. Though from a poor family, He did not hesitate to give away His clothes to needy classmates. More importantly, He never lost an opportunity to turn the minds of His friends towards God. Among other things, He formed a bhajan group for this purpose, which later became very popular.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was time to move on to Higher Secondary School, but such a school was available only in Bukkapatnam, several kilometers to the north of Puttaparthi. Young Sathya now had to trudge back and forth every day, no matter what the weather, the muddy path through fields, walking on bunds, and wading through water, as required. In the Bukkapatnam School too, He was a model student, ever helpful to others. Making students God-conscious remained His prime occupation, and to hold the attention of His mates, He would often materialise prasadam (gift-articles or vibhuti), much to their amazement. Sathya was an automatic choice for the class-leader (monitor), but this brought its share of problems. Once, His teacher asked Sathya to slap all the boys in the class for an infringement of discipline. Instead of slapping hard as he was expected to, Sathya merely patted the cheeks of the errant pupils. This greatly angered the teacher, who then directed all his wrath on the class-leader. Sathya bore the punishment in stoic silence; for Him, it was all a part of the Drama scripted by Him, and this particular scene was being enacted to impart some lessons to humanity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On another occasion, the teacher handling a particular class-hour (period) noticed that Sathya was not writing down what was being dictated, while all other students did. When questioned, Sathya replied that He was not taking down because He already knew the lesson. Interpreting this response as gross impertinence, the teacher asked Sathya to stand up on the bench, a form of punishment popular in those days. Sathya obediently did. After a while the School bell rang, signalling the end of the period in progress, and the commencement of a new period. It was time for the teacher to leave the room and make way for another one who was to handle the next period. Mr. Mahboob Khan, this other teacher, entered the classroom and to his utter surprise saw Sathya standing upon the bench. Khan loved Sathya very much, and to him it was inconceivable that Sathya would have done anything to deserve a punishment. He also noticed that the teacher who had handled the previous period was not vacating the chair. To his astonishment he then discovered that this teacher was not getting up from the chair because he was stuck or glued to it - whenever the teacher tried to get up, the chair also lifted! In a flash, Khan understood the problem. He asked Sathya to get down from the bench and the stuck teacher promptly got his release! Years later Swami disclosed that this drama was staged not to inflict humiliation on the teacher concerned but to make people conscious of His Divine powers. Humiliation is something that does not exist in Swami&amp;rsquo;s dictionary. Around this time, Mr. Seshama Raju, Sathya’s older brother, went to Kamalapuram to stay with his in-laws, and also qualify there as a teacher. Kamalapuram boasted of a good school and Seshama Raju thought that this was the school where Sathya ought to study - the entire family pinned its hope on Sathya, and dreamt that one day He would go to college and eventually end up as a big officer in the Government. And so, to Kamalapuram, Sathya went.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seshma Raju&amp;rsquo;s in-laws, being relatively well heeled, looked down upon Sathya since He was quite poor. As a result, He was not only ill-treated but also called upon to perform arduous house-hold duties. He had, for example, to fetch drinking water every day from a far-off well. Such chores left scars, which remain to this day. In the Kamalapuram School, Sathya was a great favourite of the Drill Master who doubled also as the Scout Master. Once, there was to be a grand General Fair and Cattle Show in the neighbouring village of Pushpagiri. The Scout Master wanted his troop to go Pushpagiri and render service of the type scouts were expected to. A subscription of ten rupees was collected from each boy for meeting the various expenses connected with the trip, including the bus fare. Not having the required amount, Sathya excused Himself from joining the group but assured the Scout Master that He would somehow or the other be in Pushpagiri at the appointed time for duty. While His friends went by bus, Sathya walked the entire distance, with little to eat on the way. When He finally reached Pushpagiri, He was very tired but did not flinch from discharging His duties. Just before returning, He thoughtfully bought a few small gifts for folks back home. When He returned, what greeted Him was not appreciation for the gifts but a severe punishment because His absence had created problems with the supply of drinking water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Much later, Swami revealed that He deliberately created such painful situations for Himself in order to teach the lesson of forbearance and equanimity. Despite the harsh treatment constantly administered, Swami has never ever criticised either His older brother or His sister-in-law, maintaining always that they were but mere instruments in His Drama, with specific roles to play. His teacher&amp;rsquo;s training concluded, Seshama Raju moved from Kamalapuram to Uravakonda to take appointment as a Telugu teacher in a school there. Sathya went along and joined that school. Once again, He excelled in everything, and became the cynosure of all eyes. But once He was back at home, it was the same painful routine; no let-up at all. And then, came the prophetic declaration. Sathya was stung by a scorpion one day. He was so sick that all the remedies that were used to cure him were to no avail. Eventually, the news was quickly reported to Sathya&amp;rsquo;s parents. Sathya’s parents were so heartbroken that they suspected that there could be evil spirits near him. Sathya’s father got suspicious when his behaviour changed. He armed himself with a big stick, approached Sathya, and asked &amp;ldquo;Who are You? Are You God, ghost, or devil?&amp;rdquo; The big moment had arrived and Sathya calmly replied,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am Sai.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;What are we to do with You?&amp;rdquo; Sathya replied, &amp;ldquo;Worship Me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The father&amp;rsquo;s next question was, &amp;ldquo;When?&amp;rdquo; Came the answer, &amp;ldquo;Every Thursday.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;references&#34;&gt;References&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.britannica.com/biography/Sathya-Sai-Baba&#34;&gt;https://www.britannica.com/biography/Sathya-Sai-Baba&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
