<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>e-Magazine</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/</link>
        <description>Recent content on e-Magazine</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>7 Reasons Why Bhajans Are The Simplest Way To God</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/way-to-god/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/way-to-god/</guid>
        <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s get to the point – we all know that spirituality is a practical journey of life towards Him, our Creator. A journey of life is unique to everyone – think about it, is there only ONE way to reach Him?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The whole idea of reaching God involves a myriad of angles – ranging from the complexity of meditation to the simplicity of Bhajans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The practical teachings of Sai and Hinduism in general allows the participation of every individual from any walks of life, religion, culture, ethnicity, and language. It is the way of life. We are given a choice of various sadhanas to partake in, as long as it abides by the five Human Values we’ve all come to experience by just being His devotee – Sathya, Dharma, Shanthi, Prema, Ahimsa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being born into a Sai family, I consider myself privileged to have experienced the power of Bhajans from the premature moments of my life in my mother’s womb.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BHAJANS – the beautiful convergence of Bhava (feel), Raaga (melody), and Taala (rhythm) in its simplest form is a nursery rhyme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nursery rhyme? Isn’t that something we learn when we attend kindergarten? – But if we could just think about it – Bhajans is actually a story of good over evil that is sung in a poetic and rhythmic manner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right, enough with the theories. Let’s get to the point. I believe Bhajans is the easiest way to seek and reach Him. Let me give you seven reasons why.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BLISSFUL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bliss – the purest form of happiness, love, and peace is easily attainable through the singing of God’s name. According to Swami himself:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;quote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&#34;Devotional singing induces in you a desire for experiencing the truth, to glimpse the beauty that is God, to taste the bliss that is the Self. It encourages man to dive into himself and be genuinely his real Self.&#34;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight:bold;&#34;&gt;Sathyam Shivam Sundaram VII, 497-498&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
div.quote
{
    font-style: italic; 
    text-align:center;
    margin-top: auto;
    margin-bottom: auto;
    margin-left: 2em;
    margin-right: 2em;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Give it a try – choose your favourite Bhajan, understand the story behind the song, close your eyes, and sing your hearts out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HONEST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apart from being a devotional song, Bhajans, if seen from a personalised perspective, are an honest plea to God. You do not sing for the admiration of others, nor do you play the Tabla to show your capabilities. It is a personal sadhana of every individual involved. Swami beautifully phrases it like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;quote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&#34;Devotional singing (bhajans) is the process of singing that originates in the heart, not from the lips or the tongue. It is the expression of the joyous thrill that wells up from the heart when the Glory of God is remembered. It is the spontaneous manifestation of inner ecstasy. No attention is paid to the blame or praise that others may give. It does not seek the admiration or the appreciation of the listeners.&#34;

&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight:bold;&#34;&gt;Sathyam Shivam Sundaram X, 84&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
div.quote
{
    font-style: italic; 
    text-align:center;
    margin-top: auto;
    margin-bottom: auto;
    margin-left: 2em;
    margin-right: 2em;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ATMOSPHERIC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s a fun fact – music is produced through vibrations and the sense of spiritualism is also felt through vibrations – which is why we call it &amp;ldquo;good vibes&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;bad vibes&amp;rdquo; right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exact same concept applies to Bhajan singing – a multitude of divine vibrations radiating around us, energising all those within the vicinity and beyond. Swami says:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;quote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&#34;The vibrations emanating from them make the heart vibrant. If you sing alone in your shrine, the vibrations return to you as a reaction. But in community singing, what you have is not a reaction but a wave of vibrations. They enter into the atmosphere and purify the polluted air. The atmosphere today is polluted by bad thoughts and feelings. When you sing the glory of God, the bad germs in the air are destroyed and the air gets purified by a treatment of anti-biotics, as it were.&#34;

&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight:bold;&#34;&gt;Sanathana Sarathi, January 1995, 26&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
div.quote
{
    font-style: italic; 
    text-align:center;
    margin-top: auto;
    margin-bottom: auto;
    margin-left: 2em;
    margin-right: 2em;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JOYFUL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever since I was a kid, one activity that excites me the most is Bhajans! It puts me in a mood to be happy and energised, filling me up with joyful thoughts prior, during, and post-Bhajans. Yes, there are songs with melancholic moods, but have you ever realised, in the end – we feel content, happy, and joyful. Some Bhajans make us cry but it is the tear of joy. No bhajans in the world make us tear out of anger and depression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;quote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&#34;Those who sing bhajans get what can be called a &#39;double promotion&#39;, for they derive joy and distribute joy.&#34;

&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight:bold;&#34;&gt;Sathyam Shivam Sundaram X, 101&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
div.quote
{
    font-style: italic; 
    text-align:center;
    margin-top: auto;
    margin-bottom: auto;
    margin-left: 2em;
    margin-right: 2em;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conclusively, isn&amp;rsquo;t that what we all desire? To be joyful?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ACHIEVABLE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The skill of delivering a Bhajan relies on the three essence which makes up Bhajan – Bhava, Raaga, and Taala. With constant practice, the art of feeling a Bhajan instead of performing, is easily achievable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose a song, start simple, understand the meaning, and let the visuals project in your head – you’ll get Bhava in the form of a story. Raaga and Taala will soon be of second nature to you through continuous practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, the foundation to delivering a good Bhajan is practice. This does not matter whether you’re singing in the centre or in the comfort of your own home – the goal is always, to please Him no matter the circumstances. If it’s for Him, it’s always a must to deliver the best, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;quote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&#34;Devotional singing (bhajan) is one of the processes by which you can train the mind to expand into eternal values. Teach the mind to revel in the glory and majesty of God; wean it away from petty horizons of pleasure. Devotional singing induces in you a desire for experiencing the truth, to glimpse the beauty that is God, to taste the bliss that is the Self. It encourages man to dive into himself and be genuinely his real Self.&#34;

&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight:bold;&#34;&gt;Sathyam Shivam Sundaram VII, 497-498&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
div.quote
{
    font-style: italic; 
    text-align:center;
    margin-top: auto;
    margin-bottom: auto;
    margin-left: 2em;
    margin-right: 2em;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NUTRITIOUS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bhajans feed the body, mind, and soul with positive energy – the only nutrient needed in the path to attain Moksha. When we participate in Bhajans, we train the mind to constantly chant the name of various deities in various languages and tunes, empowering ourselves with the energy and motion to lead us back to THE source.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;quote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&#34;Some people... question the propriety of calling God by means of... a multiplicity of names. But each name is indicative of only one aspect of Divinity. It denotes a single part of the Supreme Personality... Every name is but a facet, a part, a ray of the Supreme. The spiritual discipline consists in recognising and becoming aware of the One that supports and sustains the many. That is the precious gem of wisdom that one must secure and treasure.&#34;

&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight:bold;&#34;&gt;Sathyam Shivam Sundaram X, 87&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
div.quote
{
    font-style: italic; 
    text-align:center;
    margin-top: auto;
    margin-bottom: auto;
    margin-left: 2em;
    margin-right: 2em;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is, in a nutshell – the essence of spirituality. The various forms we favour are just mere avenues to channel our energy towards the right direction, but we all know there is only one God, and He is omnipresent. Bhajans, help us realise that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPIRITUAL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From what has been derived so far, I personally feel Bhajans encompasses what we call spirituality. It embodies the SAI in us, guides us towards the right path, with various accessible avenues to enable everyone to participate in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let us not forget, participating in Bhajans does not only happen in the centre by being part of the Bhajan Team. In fact, the Bhajan Team just acts as a guide to standardise and ensure high-quality Bhajans are delivered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But in the end, what makes Bhajans the simplest form of spiritual sadhana is the way it is designed – it can be conducted anywhere, whether in a group or individually as long as there is a firm conviction to reach Swami. It amazes me how personal yet collective Bhajans are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have not realised yet, my seven points actually lie within the word &amp;ldquo;Bhajans&amp;rdquo; – &amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;B&lt;/strong&gt;lissful, &lt;strong&gt;H&lt;/strong&gt;onest, &lt;strong&gt;A&lt;/strong&gt;tmospheric, &lt;strong&gt;J&lt;/strong&gt;oyful, &lt;strong&gt;A&lt;/strong&gt;chievable, &lt;strong&gt;N&lt;/strong&gt;utritious, &lt;strong&gt;S&lt;/strong&gt;piritual&amp;rdquo;. Never forget that answers are always in the questions we ask – it is never that far. It just requires effort and dedication with a pure heart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Human Values Drawing</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/hv-drawing/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/hv-drawing/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/hv-drawing/img_hemmaraj_hiran_1.JPG" alt="Featured image of post Human Values Drawing" /&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This artwork reflects the Human Values that I have learnt from my weekly Balvikas and bhajan class in centre / online classes. It makes me to be self-disciplined. I also remember that Swami said to practice &amp;ldquo;Truth, Honesty and Fairness&amp;rdquo;. I also learned meditation so that I can keep myself happy. I am always reminded of Swami&amp;rsquo;s saying - &amp;ldquo;I am always with you, in you, above you and around you&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;Gallery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/hv-drawing/img_hemmaraj_hiran_1.JPG&#34; data-size=&#34;810x1080&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/hv-drawing/img_hemmaraj_hiran_1_hu2367bd119754f828d0420bafd432622b_98476_480x0_resize_q75_box.JPG 480w, ./p/hv-drawing/img_hemmaraj_hiran_1_hu2367bd119754f828d0420bafd432622b_98476_1024x0_resize_q75_box.JPG 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/hv-drawing/img_hemmaraj_hiran_1.JPG&#34; width=&#34;810&#34; height=&#34;1080&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;figure&gt;
		&lt;a href=&#34;./p/hv-drawing/img_hemmaraj_hiran_2.JPG&#34; data-size=&#34;1080x810&#34;&gt;
			&lt;img srcset=&#34;./p/hv-drawing/img_hemmaraj_hiran_2_hu39498bb00db76096c6c3577fc7c43bb7_97863_480x0_resize_q75_box.JPG 480w, ./p/hv-drawing/img_hemmaraj_hiran_2_hu39498bb00db76096c6c3577fc7c43bb7_97863_1024x0_resize_q75_box.JPG 1024w&#34;
				src=&#34;./p/hv-drawing/img_hemmaraj_hiran_2.JPG&#34; width=&#34;1080&#34; height=&#34;810&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
				alt=&#34;&amp;nbsp;&#34;&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
		
	&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Diya&#39;s Love for Swami</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/diyas-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/diyas-love/</guid>
        <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Diya is an eight-year-old cheerful girl, witty and loving. One day as Diya was playing, she thought to herself &amp;ldquo;Why don&amp;rsquo;t I have a tea party with Swami? Swami will be delighted.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As she went on preparing for the tea party, she was in a hurry to make it the perfect party. However, her house was in a mess and she was upset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At that moment, her friend Arjun was cycling past her house. Diya called out to Arjun and asked him if he could help her clean the house. Arjun agreed and started to help Diya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As time flew, the place was cleaned up and the tea party was ready. The tea had been made by her mother along with freshly baked cookies from the oven and Diya had changed into a beautiful pink dress. Diya thanked Arjun and told him that she was now waiting for Swami.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hearing this, Arjun said, &amp;ldquo;Dear Diya, I am already here, don&amp;rsquo;t you realize who I am?&amp;rdquo;. At this point, Diya saw a lovely image of her beloved Swami on the face of Arjun and was amazed with the image she saw. She hadn&amp;rsquo;t realised that Arjun was all along, her beloved Swami. &amp;ldquo;Oh Swami! I didn&amp;rsquo;t realise it was YOU!  Swami replied, &amp;ldquo;Diya, I&amp;rsquo;m always in you, with you and around you, no matter what. Come let&amp;rsquo;s have our tea now&amp;rdquo;, said Swami and Diya smiled, so pleased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As she was having her tea, she heard a loud bell go off &amp;ldquo;Ringggggg&amp;hellip;..&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Diya, Diya wake up. It&amp;rsquo;s time for school&amp;rdquo;. It was the sound of her mother waking her up. Diya woke up as the morning sun shone on her face along with its lovely breeze, as her mother drew the curtains open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this point, Diya realised that her tea party with Swami was all but a dream. Remembering her dream, she broke into a beautiful smile, as she heard Swami’s words once again in her ears:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Diya I&amp;rsquo;m always in you, with you and around you, no matter what.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Having A Best Friend</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/best-friend/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/best-friend/</guid>
        <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This story tells that two friends were walking through a desert. During some point of the journey they had an argument, and one friend slapped the other one in the face.The one who got slapped was hurt, but without saying anything, wrote in the sand&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Today my best friend slapped me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They kept on walking until they found an oasis, where they decided to take a bath. The one who had been slapped got stuck in the mire and started drowning, but the friend saved him. After he recovered from the near drowning, he wrote on a stone;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Today my best friend saved my life.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The friend who had slapped and saved his best friend asked him;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;After I hurt you, you wrote in the sand and now, you write on a stone, why?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other friend replied;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;When someone hurts us we should write it down in sand where winds of forgiveness can erase it away. But, when someone does something good for us, we must engrave it in stone where no wind can ever erase it.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Jai Jai Manamohana</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/jai-jai/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/jai-jai/</guid>
        <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;bhajan---jai-jai-manamohana&#34;&gt;Bhajan - Jai Jai Manamohana&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;audio controls class=&#34;marginauto&#34;&gt;
    &lt;source src=&#34;https://docs.google.com/uc?export=open&amp;id=1W-bkD3vSDG4LPcETdLcbzBhUL2ncLLfL&#34; type=&#34;audio/mp3&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;source src=&#34;https://docs.google.com/uc?export=open&amp;id=1W-bkD3vSDG4LPcETdLcbzBhUL2ncLLfL&#34; type=&#34;audio/ogg&#34; /&gt;
    Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
    .marginauto {
        margin: 10px auto 20px;
        display: block;
    }
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Janani Janani</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/janani-janani/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/janani-janani/</guid>
        <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;bhajan---janani-janani&#34;&gt;Bhajan - Janani Janani&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;audio controls class=&#34;marginauto&#34;&gt;
    &lt;source src=&#34;https://docs.google.com/uc?export=open&amp;id=1UkH4kOfCqQc7QD31PAq6Vj6uxqSRtT6w&#34; type=&#34;audio/mp3&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;source src=&#34;https://docs.google.com/uc?export=open&amp;id=1UkH4kOfCqQc7QD31PAq6Vj6uxqSRtT6w&#34; type=&#34;audio/ogg&#34; /&gt;
    Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
    .marginauto {
        margin: 10px auto 20px;
        display: block;
    }
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Two Friends &amp; The Bear</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/friends-bear/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/friends-bear/</guid>
        <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vijay and Raju were friends. On a holiday they went walking into a forest, enjoying the beauty of nature. Suddenly they saw a bear coming at them. They became frightened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Raju, who knew all about climbing trees, ran up to a tree and climbed up quickly. He didn’t think of Vijay. Vijay had no idea how to climb a tree.
Vijay thought for a second. He has heard before that animals don’t prefer to eat dead bodies, so he fell to the ground and held his breath. The bear sniffed him and thought he was dead. So, it went on its way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Raju asked Vijay;  &amp;ldquo;What did the bear whisper into your ears?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vijay replied, &amp;ldquo;The bear asked me to keep away from friends like you&amp;rdquo; and went on his way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moral of the story: 
A friend in need is a friend indeed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;references&#34;&gt;References&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wealthygorilla.com/best-short-moral-stories/#forward#forward&#34;&gt;https://wealthygorilla.com/best-short-moral-stories/#forward#forward&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Abundance is Divine Will</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/divine-will/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/divine-will/</guid>
        <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aum Shri Sairam.  Salutations to Bhagawan Sri Sathya Sai Baba, and thank you Swami for all the blessings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dedication: I thank my beloved wife for her courage and composure and her unflagging love and support for the duration of my recent hospitalisation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It started with an unusual busy travel week, the 18th to 23rd February 2018. I drove a honeymoon couple on a tour, covering Malacca, Kuala Lumpur and Genting Highlands. But on the 21st February itself, I was already feeling a little unwell. On that day, I came back home early, by 5 pm, and rested. But by Friday, the 23rd February, I was getting weaker, and on that day, I asked my wife Santhi to drive, while I accompanied her. We dropped the guests at the airport and returned home. Santhi insisted on taking me to our family doctor&amp;rsquo;s clinic. The doctor thought it was just a normal cough, and prescribed antibiotics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Tuesday the 27th, the situation was worsening, and I went to the clinic again. This time, the doctor put me on drips, and treated me to two rounds of nebulizer. While the doctor wanted to admit me, I did not want to be admitted. I had a problem in my workplace because a driver had put in a sudden resignation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was driving the van, all the while coughing badly. Santhi stayed with me all the time. As my condition got worse, she courageously took on the driver role. I continued the acute coughing, and soon the vomiting started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We dropped off all the students we were ferrying, and she drove me to the Klang General Hospital Emergency Department. I was put in a wheelchair and rushed to the Red Zone. I was panting quite badly by then, out of breath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was immediately put on drips, and the doctors started examining me. As I waited for admission, I told Santhi to go back and rest. By 4 am, I was brought to ward 8B, and closely monitored by doctors. Blood samples were taken for various tests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My wife came in early the next morning, and the doctor explained my condition. She left around noon to drive the van to pick up the school students. But as she was on her way, the hospital called her. My condition had deteriorated quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She quickly managed to get someone to help to drive the van and rushed to the hospital. The doctors told her that my condition was critical, and I had to be moved to the ICU.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All I remember is being wheeled to the ICU, and the security guard stopping my wife following me inside. I was in tears. Everything happened so quickly. I was transferred to the bed, my clothes changed and the tubes and gadgets attached. I was always aware of all the happenings but felt weak and in a daze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moments of bliss&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From this moment I lost track of time. My only thought was, &amp;ldquo;Baba, I am surrendering to you&amp;rdquo;. No other thoughts there onwards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I felt a strange sense of relaxation and thoughtlessness and began enjoying the moments of peace and bliss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every day, during the visiting hours, Santhi would rush to me and assure me that I was alright - &amp;ldquo;Babe, you are doing good&amp;rdquo;. She would keep applying Vibhuti on my chest and on my forehead. The smell of Vibhutii was everywhere throughout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My posture on the bed was relaxed and so comfortable that I felt no pain at all. I was constantly in the same cool, happy mode! No worries at all. I just knew that during every visiting hour, many would come. They would touch me and comfort me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was not wearing my spectacles, but recognized almost everyone who came. The touch and prayer and comforting words made me constantly in a positive mood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doctors attended to me day and night – I could hear them as they spoke. And whenever I opened my eyes, they would ask how I was doing and how I felt. I would always respond that I was fine, and give a thumbs up. I was honestly feeling well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Divine moments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Often I would suddenly hear chanting (with energy like the early morning Omkar at Prashanti). I would open my eyes, and see no one at my side. I would close my eyes again, and just enjoy the moments of bliss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then one day, a doctor told me that I was tired, and that he was going to put me on a relaxation medication. The next thing I knew&amp;hellip; I felt myself hanging… my mind was calling &amp;ldquo;Mohana&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;  but the body was just hanging. As I enjoyed these moments of calm and peace, suddenly I saw a few tall angel-like figure&amp;hellip; dressed in white&amp;hellip; I watched them&amp;hellip; until they disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the days went by, many strange incidents happened. One day I had a dream&amp;hellip; my late mom appeared before me. She said, &amp;ldquo;There is nothing to worry&amp;hellip;  everything will be alright.&amp;rdquo; Another day, my late brother and I were in a dream, sitting near my office, outside the building facing the car park. We were sitting and talking casually. In front of us, my dark blue Volkswagen van was parked. Suddenly my brother asked me to take a look at the Audi 2 seater left hand drive car, hidden, beside the Volkswagen. And suddenly, the scene disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whenever I woke up after these dreams, I felt reassured that I was alright, and will be out of hospital soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once my wife came, looking very tired. She told me, &amp;ldquo;Babe, I just meditated and sent the light energy to you. You take care. I will come and see you tomorrow.&amp;rdquo; I just nodded. That same night, I saw a triple bulb laser pointer-like light, blinking a pinkish light, with seven shades of colours, very short and swift bursts of light.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dream or hallucination?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bro Harwinrao used to always visit me, and one day he told me, &amp;ldquo;Uncle we checked, all are ok except a few are having negative energy.&amp;rdquo; What he was referring to were bundles of humans hanging in the curtain railing in a dark blue cloth! Was this a dream? Or hallucination? When I opened my eyes, I did not see anyone - I had a similar experience when I was in the ward upon being moved out of the ICU.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was always coated with Vibuthi – I was assured that Swami is always there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As soon I was admitted in the ICU, I saw two lines - one upper line and a lower line (l considered this the consciousness line). Each time I reached the top line I would feel enjoyment and calm. At times I started to be at the lower line – and I would feel the attachment, and then would come the cough, with my nose sensitive to odour, heat / warmth of people coming close to me. If anyone came with perfume, I got a suffocating feeling. Feeling the discomfort, I would close my eyes and stay calm to move to the upper line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Daily the nurses will bathe me – it was always at 11pm, and that was the only time I was aware of. They would wash me with hot/ warm water, using shower cream. I would feel very clean - no body odour whatsoever while in ICU. In short it was a very blissful life!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The doctors and nurses would explain clearly everything that they intended to do, so I would be fully aware of the process. For example I need to swallow when the milk is fed every 3 hourly. The oxygen mask also had to be frequently changed, depending on the reading on the gadgets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of the above could be hallucinations, dreams or visions influenced from my past learning experiences or memory recollections. Some of the moments are difficult to explain. But for more than 90% of the time, I was awake and aware, certainly not asleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In spite of the seriousness of the ailment, the overall experience was not unpleasant, and credit goes to Swami, to my dear wife, and to all those loving souls who prayed intensely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What I did not know&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I was having this experience, others heard that my condition was deteriorating – the doctor gave a mere 20% chance of survival !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On 2nd March, as I was in the ward using Continuous Positive Airway Pressure (CPAP), before the Oxygen level saturated below 90. Then I was moved to the High Dependency unit. An urgent SOS – a call for intensified prayers went out. Messages on whatsapp would urge, &amp;ldquo;Let us do a group Gayatri Chanting, 9 times at 9pm tonight, for our dear lovely Bro Mohana who is admitted in GH Klang for pneumonia. Our group prayers will help him recover and be back to normalcy speedily&amp;hellip; set a reminder on your phone.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A second SOS, on March 3rd urged, &amp;ldquo;Sairam dear All. Please continue your prayers. Bro Mohana is in Klang GH ICU Ward under assisted ventilation and antibiotics. We need to pray specifically for Swami to give him the strength to recover.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After this - on Sunday, my wife and Sis Anjulah asked me whether I would like to have any gadget like an iPod or iPhone to listen to Bhajans, but I declined. I explained the two lines I continued to see as consciousness, and I was enjoying the blissful experience all the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whenever my wife or anyone put their hands on my chest, I could feel the stress they were going through. I even reassured my wife, &amp;ldquo;Sayang, I am fine and you just need to relax - I can feel your tension in the form of weight in your arm.&amp;rdquo; Sometimes I could even smell the toxin in Santhi&amp;rsquo;s breath, and told her to go and see a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She would tell me everyone is praying for me, she was always very courageous – she made me move on the single line upward and maintain my composure and inner peace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I must express my heartfelt gratitude to each and every staff member of HTAR, Klang. They are angels, born to serve, and they do this passionately and dedicatedly, attending to every request from urinal pan to bed pan. They took care of me, leaving no room for any complaint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Divine Lullaby</title>
        <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/the-divine-lullaby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/the-divine-lullaby/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/the-divine-lullaby/markandeya.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Divine Lullaby" /&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The story of Queen Madālasā is in Chapters 25-30 of the &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://practicalphilosophy.org.au/extras/mada-lasa/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Mārkaṇḍeya Purāṇa&lt;/a&gt;. The Mārkaṇḍeya is one of the eighteen ‘great Purāṇas’ (Mahāpurāṇas) relating to Brahmā, said to have been narrated by the Riṛṣi Mārkaṇḍeya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this mythological tale, Queen Madālasā&amp;rsquo;s newborn child was named by the King. Upon hearing the name given by the King, the baby started to cry out loud. Madālasā sings this beautiful lullaby to pacify the child.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-divine-lullaby&#34;&gt;The Divine Lullaby&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/uDd3iupKUyI&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;translation&#34;&gt;Translation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Meaning&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Why are you crying?&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;You are pure&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The name you have acquired is not yours, merely a mind-created fiction applied to you&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The body is not you, nor are you of it&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The Lord of the universe doesn&amp;rsquo;t cry either!&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;This sound is an illusion attributed to you&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The qualities imagined as yours are inherent in all the senses&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The insignificant elements within the man acquire the condition of growth through the addition of food, water and drink&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;It is not a growth or diminution of You&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Within the body shell&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;You remain constant&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Do not become confounded by this body which has been fastened upon you&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Father, Son, Mother, Wife, Mine, Not Mine&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Do not assign much significance to what is only an aggregation of elements&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The deluded man thinks pains alleviate pain&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The deluded man thinks enjoyment of pleasures gives happiness&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The intelligent man whose mind is free from confusion knows pleasures and sorrows to be alike&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The carriage goes upon the earth, the body is seated in the carriage&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The Self resides within the body&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The deluded Jiva thinks &amp;ldquo;I am this body&amp;rdquo;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;The Self has no attachement to His carriage&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Foolish is such ignorance!&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
