<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Group 2 on e-Magazine</title>
    <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/tags/group-2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Group 2 on e-Magazine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/tags/group-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Human Values Drawing</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/hv-drawing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/hv-drawing/</guid>
      <description>This artwork reflects the Human Values that I have learnt from my weekly Balvikas and bhajan class in centre / online classes. It makes me to be self-disciplined. I also remember that Swami said to practice &amp;ldquo;Truth, Honesty and Fairness&amp;rdquo;. I also learned meditation so that I can keep myself happy. I am always reminded of Swami&amp;rsquo;s saying - &amp;ldquo;I am always with you, in you, above you and around you&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diya&#39;s Love for Swami</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/diyas-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/diyas-love/</guid>
      <description>Diya is an eight-year-old cheerful girl, witty and loving. One day as Diya was playing, she thought to herself &amp;ldquo;Why don&amp;rsquo;t I have a tea party with Swami? Swami will be delighted.&amp;rdquo;
As she went on preparing for the tea party, she was in a hurry to make it the perfect party. However, her house was in a mess and she was upset.
At that moment, her friend Arjun was cycling past her house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Having A Best Friend</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/best-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/best-friend/</guid>
      <description>This story tells that two friends were walking through a desert. During some point of the journey they had an argument, and one friend slapped the other one in the face.The one who got slapped was hurt, but without saying anything, wrote in the sand
 &amp;ldquo;Today my best friend slapped me.&amp;rdquo;
 They kept on walking until they found an oasis, where they decided to take a bath. The one who had been slapped got stuck in the mire and started drowning, but the friend saved him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jai Jai Manamohana</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/jai-jai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/jai-jai/</guid>
      <description> Bhajan - Jai Jai Manamohana Your browser does not support the audio element..marginauto {margin: 10px auto 20px;display: block;}  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Janani Janani</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/janani-janani/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/janani-janani/</guid>
      <description> Bhajan - Janani Janani Your browser does not support the audio element..marginauto {margin: 10px auto 20px;display: block;}  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Friends &amp; The Bear</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/friends-bear/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/friends-bear/</guid>
      <description>Vijay and Raju were friends. On a holiday they went walking into a forest, enjoying the beauty of nature. Suddenly they saw a bear coming at them. They became frightened.
Raju, who knew all about climbing trees, ran up to a tree and climbed up quickly. He didn’t think of Vijay. Vijay had no idea how to climb a tree. Vijay thought for a second. He has heard before that animals don’t prefer to eat dead bodies, so he fell to the ground and held his breath.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
