<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on e-Magazine</title>
    <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on e-Magazine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Manasa Bhajare Unplugged</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/manasa-bhajare-unplugged/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/manasa-bhajare-unplugged/</guid>
      <description>Music has always been my passion and the means through which I connect to the Lord. This is a simple offering to render my love to Swami through the first bhajan that He introduced to His devotees.
Manasa Bhajare Guru Charanam Dustara Bhava Sagara Taranam Guru Maharaj Guru Jai Jai Sainatha Sadguru Jai Jai Sathya Sainatha Sadguru Jai Jai Om Namah Shivaya Om Namah Shivaya Om Namah Shivaya Shivaya Namah Om Arunachala Shiva Arunachala Shiva Arunachala Shiva Aruna Shivom Omkaram Bhava Omkaram Bhava Omkaram Bhava Om Namo Baba Meaning:O mind!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Story of Goddess Annapoorani</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/goddess-annapoorani/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/goddess-annapoorani/</guid>
      <description>One day, Lord Shiva and Goddess Parvati had a disagreement. She disappeared and said she would like to see how the world would survive without her.
In the disappearance of Goddess Parvati, the whole world was begging for food. To find a solution, Lord Shiva went to Kashi. There in Kashi, He saw Goddess Parvati in the form of Goddess Annapoorani (an aspect of Devi and is known as the goddess of food and nourishment) distributing food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bhajan</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/bhajan-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/bhajan-song/</guid>
      <description>Sairam, My name is Thareni and I am 16 years old. The title of my song offering is Bada Chittha Chora Brindavana Sanchara. I learned this song in my Balvikas. The meaning of this song talks about the greatest stealer of hearts who roams through Brindavan - Lord Krishna. The song talks about Lord Krishna as the child who plays the flute and who lifted the Govardhana Hill. He is also referred to as the cowherd boy who captivated the minds of His devotees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOVE = HAPPINESS</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/love-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/love-happiness/</guid>
      <description>Swami simplifies our understanding of the principle of love with a saying: &amp;ldquo;Love in thought is Sathya, Love in action is Dharma, Love in feeling is Shanti and Love in understanding is Ahimsa&amp;rdquo;. Love is the hidden current for all the human values. When we speak with love, it is Sathya. When work is saturated with love, it is Dharma. Life lived according to these values gives peace. Love coming from a peaceful heart brings bliss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save The Ocean (Diorama)</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/save-ocean/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/save-ocean/</guid>
      <description>Oceans cover 71% of the planet and are home to important species and ecosystems that we rely on for food, livelihoods, climate regulation and more. But the oceans need our help. Saving the oceans can sometimes feel like an overwhelming task, but if we all pitch in, we can make a big difference.
We can save the ocean by practising the following habits:
 Conserve Water. Use less water so excess runoff and wastewater will not flow into the ocean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Divine Lullaby</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/the-divine-lullaby/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/the-divine-lullaby/</guid>
      <description>The story of Queen Madālasā is in Chapters 25-30 of the Mārkaṇḍeya Purāṇa. The Mārkaṇḍeya is one of the eighteen ‘great Purāṇas’ (Mahāpurāṇas) relating to Brahmā, said to have been narrated by the Riṛṣi Mārkaṇḍeya.
In this mythological tale, Queen Madālasā&amp;rsquo;s newborn child was named by the King. Upon hearing the name given by the King, the baby started to cry out loud. Madālasā sings this beautiful lullaby to pacify the child.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
