<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on e-Magazine</title>
    <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on e-Magazine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Divine Grace</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/divine-grace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/divine-grace/</guid>
      <description>Gita Samarpanam is a group born out of the vision and initiation of Aunty Jegadeva to recite the verses of Chapter 12 on Bhakti Yoga or Path of Devotion from the most revered holy book - the Bhagavad Gita. It is to be an offering to Bhagawan on Ladies Day for the year 2020.
I grabbed this opportunity to be a part of the sadhana not only as an offering but more importantly to learn to chant the verses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family is EVERYTHING</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/family-is-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/family-is-everything/</guid>
      <description>Amidst the widespread of Covid-19 we have all been lifted into another way of living. Our lives have been slowed down by an amazingly small organism with a huge amount of power. In March 2020, when the Movement Control Order was announced, there was sudden fear and panic everywhere.
Each day presented us with a new set of rules and changes that gave us a reason to pause. Schools closing, kids zoning out during endless Zoom classes, holiday plans cancelled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seek And You Will Find The Inner Peace You Crave</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/inner-peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/inner-peace/</guid>
      <description>When the coronavirus pandemic reached our shores and the Movement Control Order was announced, I was paradoxically elated. For I chose to look at the positive side, I decided that it was a great opportunity to take a breather from the hectic pace of life that I had become accustomed to. Rather then dwell on the negativity and worry unnecessarily over a virus that was restricting our way of life, I decided to make the most of the situation as best I could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service of Love</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/service-of-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/service-of-love/</guid>
      <description>Why doing service is important to you? How does the seva improve you as a person as a spiritual aspirant as a guru? Well, I don’t know that seva means performing without expecting a reward, or a result of an outcome. Little I know that Seva is a powerful tool to learn about myself, be it inner or outer. I was doing it for my grandmother, father, mom, siblings, and my school teachers continuously since I was a little girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Baba Chose Parthi</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/baba-and-parthi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/baba-and-parthi/</guid>
      <description>Below are some insights into different words/names related to Swami’s place in India and its significance to us as His devotees.
 Bharatha (India) → Bha + Ra+ Tha → feeling (bhava) – tune (raga) – rhythm (taala). Anantapur (city in Andhra Pradesh) → Ananta = infinite, pur = body.
 A devotee should have staunch faith like the Mountain Penukonda (mount/fort in Anantapur city) –&amp;gt; Penu means big, konda means mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love All Serve All</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/love-all-serve-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/love-all-serve-all/</guid>
      <description>
 Gallery  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love for Swami</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/love-for-swami/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/love-for-swami/</guid>
      <description>When I sing the Glory of Swami, I will think of Him residing in my heart. I feel that He is listening to me singing happily. It also gives me the pleasure humming His names. I hope Baba will enjoy listening to me singing. This is my way of showing my love towards Him. Sai Ram
 Bhajan - Guru Baba Guru Baba Your browser does not support the audio element.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Bhajan</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/my-bhajan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/my-bhajan/</guid>
      <description>I learned this song in my Balvikas. The meaning of this song is O mind, worship the Lotus Feet of your God and Supreme Teacher, Sai Baba who will take you safely across the ocean of Samsara. Victory to our Lord and supreme Teacher, Sai Nath! To chant and worship the divine names of Lord Shiva who dwells on the Arunachala mountain and Sai Baba whose form is OM. Lastly, the reason why I like to sing this song is because it is very meaningful and Swami sang when he was 14 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Happy Family</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/my-happy-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/my-happy-family/</guid>
      <description>This is my happy family. I love my family.
 Gallery Family House
Garden Vacation
 Some of the pictures I drew.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manasa Bhajore Guru Charanam</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/manasa-bhajore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/manasa-bhajore/</guid>
      <description> Manasa Bhajore Guru Charanam With swami teaching I have learn how to love and care to others
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Divine Lullaby</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/the-divine-lullaby/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/the-divine-lullaby/</guid>
      <description>The story of Queen Madālasā is in Chapters 25-30 of the Mārkaṇḍeya Purāṇa. The Mārkaṇḍeya is one of the eighteen ‘great Purāṇas’ (Mahāpurāṇas) relating to Brahmā, said to have been narrated by the Riṛṣi Mārkaṇḍeya.
In this mythological tale, Queen Madālasā&amp;rsquo;s newborn child was named by the King. Upon hearing the name given by the King, the baby started to cry out loud. Madālasā sings this beautiful lullaby to pacify the child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
