<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on e-Magazine</title>
    <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on e-Magazine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>God names</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/god-names/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/god-names/</guid>
      <description>Crossword Puzzle Makerdiv.quote{font-style: italic; text-align:center;margin-top: auto;margin-bottom: auto;margin-left: 2em;margin-right: 2em;}  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You Sai</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/thank-you-sai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/thank-you-sai/</guid>
      <description>I am blessed With your love that makes me whole Your love that never takes a toll. No pen can ever explain the divine love, The feeling I am trying to explain Yet all creations cannot seem to stop talking about it. You taught us love You showered us with love, I learned that love, I showed that love. &#34;All things are beautiful seen through the eyes of love&#34; you said, That&#39;s when I knew I was beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why fear when I am here?</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/quote/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/quote/</guid>
      <description>Bhagawan says, &amp;ldquo;Why fear when I am here&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;Fear&amp;rdquo; means fear of anything, imaginary or real, danger, disaster, or death. &amp;ldquo;When&amp;rdquo; means anytime, or all the time. &amp;ldquo;I am here&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;I am everywhere, I AM IN YOU and not outside you, not separate from you, wherever I am; in Prashanthi Nilayam, Brindavan or anywhere else.
In conclusion, we have no reason to fear as we have the Lord in our midst and have Him placed in our hearts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bhajans &amp; Discipline</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/bhajans-and-discipline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/bhajans-and-discipline/</guid>
      <description>Bhajan is not merely an activity done for fun. Yes, it is a lot of fun to sing and be involved in bhajans, but at the same time it is a form of sadhana, a spiritual practice and even a form of Seva as the duty of a bhajan singer is to invoke devotion in oneself and others. Therefore, having said that, this means that discipline forms an integral part of the responsibility of a bhajan singer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Painting with Calligraphy Art</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/calligraphy-painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/calligraphy-painting/</guid>
      <description> The background painting was inspired by pastel blue and pink aesthetics. A 95th birthday wish to Baba was lettered in calligraphic font. Some of Swami’s incredible quotes were written as well. Some details and decorations were added too.
 Gallery  
 References https://youtu.be/9RwKGTMFhbo
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Divine Lullaby</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/the-divine-lullaby/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/the-divine-lullaby/</guid>
      <description>The story of Queen Madālasā is in Chapters 25-30 of the Mārkaṇḍeya Purāṇa. The Mārkaṇḍeya is one of the eighteen ‘great Purāṇas’ (Mahāpurāṇas) relating to Brahmā, said to have been narrated by the Riṛṣi Mārkaṇḍeya.
In this mythological tale, Queen Madālasā&amp;rsquo;s newborn child was named by the King. Upon hearing the name given by the King, the baby started to cry out loud. Madālasā sings this beautiful lullaby to pacify the child.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
