<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Group 4 on The Awakening</title>
    <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/tags/group-4/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Group 4 on The Awakening</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/tags/group-4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nature Is God, God Is Nature</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/nature-is-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/nature-is-god/</guid>
      <description>We need to respect nature and living things because the environment is important. I know that hurting the environment in various ways impacts all beings and pollutes the Earth in the long run. Without plants and trees we would not be able to survive. The environment is also good and healthy for us. It helps us to live in the way we please.
Nature is the most important thing in our lives and everyone should know about its importance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You Sai</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/thank-you-sai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/thank-you-sai/</guid>
      <description>I am blessed With your love that makes me whole Your love that never takes a toll. No pen can ever explain the divine love, The feeling I am trying to explain Yet all creations cannot seem to stop talking about it. You taught us love You showered us with love, I learned that love, I showed that love. &#34;All things are beautiful seen through the eyes of love&#34; you said, That&#39;s when I knew I was beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Are My Sai</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/poem-my-sai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/poem-my-sai/</guid>
      <description> Poem - You Are My Sai  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bhajan Explained</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/bhajan-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/bhajan-song/</guid>
      <description>Sairam, My name is Thareni and I am 16 years old. The title of my song offering is Bada Chittha Chora Brindavana Sanchara. I learned this song in my Balvikas. The meaning of this song talks about the greatest stealer of hearts who roams through Brindavan - Lord Krishna. The song talks about Lord Krishna as the child who plays the flute and who lifted the Govardhana Hill. He is also referred to as the cowherd boy who captivated the minds of His devotees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prasadam with Love</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/prasadam-with-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/prasadam-with-love/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
