<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Group 3 on The Awakening</title>
    <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/tags/group-3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Group 3 on The Awakening</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/tags/group-3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>C.O.L.O.U.R.S</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/mandala-colours/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/mandala-colours/</guid>
      <description>What is a Mandala? The Mandala word comes from Sanskrit and means “What holds together “. It is a circle that symbolizes the cosmos and the circle of life. It is formed by a centre and drawings that flow into it. In the Orient, it is linked to the art of meditation, in fact, it is used to focus on the “centre of life”.
“Coloring mandalas allows the brain to enter a peaceful state and to be focused on filling in the geometrical shapes instead of thinking about their worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guru - Bringing you Brightness</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/guru/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/guru/</guid>
      <description> In this drawing I am illustrating a disciple sitting in front of his guru and listening to the knowledge imparted by the guru.
 Gallery  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Tamil New Year</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/happy-tamil-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/happy-tamil-new-year/</guid>
      <description> Gallery  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome the New year with an Elephant</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/welcome-the-new-year-with-an-elephant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/welcome-the-new-year-with-an-elephant/</guid>
      <description> Gallery  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Earth Day Art</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/earth-day-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/earth-day-art/</guid>
      <description>Earth Day is mostly celebrated by performing outdoor activities individually or in groups. Activities such as planting trees, picking up roadside trash, conducting various programs for motivating sustainable living like making use of recycled materials, are performed. Some people also sign petitions to governments, calling for effective and immediate action to stop global warming and to reverse environmental damage.
Earth Day is not a public holiday. Programs at school, institutional levels are conducted to raise awareness among children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Earth Day Painting</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/earth-day-painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/earth-day-painting/</guid>
      <description>A mountain landscape art work which was inspired by one of my idol’s painting from a reality show which I watched recently. The quote, “Nature is the art of God” was added to show that we should protect and love our nature wholeheartedly. Happy Earth Day to everyone who lives in our beloved God’s green earth.
 Gallery  
 References The K-pop band BTS’s member, Jeon Jungkook’s mountain side painting from their reality show “ BTS In The Soop”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A sketch of Lord Shiva</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/shiva-sketch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/shiva-sketch/</guid>
      <description>Gallery</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>e-poster for Mahashivarathri and Earth Day</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/eposter-mahashivarathri/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/eposter-mahashivarathri/</guid>
      <description>My e-poster for Mahashivarathri and Earth Day
 Link Mahashivarathri: https://www.powtoon.com/s/cXQZMLXvWQK/1/m
Earth Day: https://www.powtoon.com/s/eDlUn2iyRc6/1/m</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earth Day</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/earth-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/earth-day/</guid>
      <description>What is Earth Day? Earth Day is a day we celebrate to show our love and appreciation to mother nature. This day is really important because we humans are starting to polluting the earth and making a mess in it. We also do some cleaning events all around the world so that we can live peacefully and happily again!
Why do we celebrate Earth Day? Aren’t we supposed to be thankful for living in this magnificent and beautiful earth?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earth Day Poem</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/earth-day-poem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/earth-day-poem/</guid>
      <description>My mother, sister, and I brainstormed and wrote the poem. My mother then helped me with the layout. The layout was completed using the Microsoft Word program. The images are from Microsoft stock images.
 Gallery 
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspirational Women Crossword Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/inspirational-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/inspirational-women/</guid>
      <description>I researched inspirational women from the last century. My mother and I then worked on the clues and we generated the using an online puzzle generator.
 Gallery 
 References From Pankhurst to Pink: 100 of the most inspiring women from the last 100 years | Marie Claire https://worksheets.theteacherscorner.net/make-your-own/crossword/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lingashtakam Keyboard Recital</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/lingashtakam-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/lingashtakam-keyboard/</guid>
      <description> I practiced the verses on my keyboard a few times. When I was confident, I played and my mother recorded it for me.
 Lingashtakam verses keyboard recital by Dhaanya Nathan  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahashivarathri &amp; International Women&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/mahashivarathri-womens-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/mahashivarathri-womens-day/</guid>
      <description> Gallery  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahashivarathri - Shiva &amp; Shakti</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/shiva-shakti-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/shiva-shakti-art/</guid>
      <description> The Godhead, of which the masculine, passive, transcendent, eternal principle is Shiva, and the feminine, active, immanent, temporal principle is Shakti, the divine Mother.
 Gallery  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of Maha Shivaratri</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/story-mahashivaratri/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/story-mahashivaratri/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time the Devas and Asuras were churning the Samudra Manthan (churning of the ocean of milk) to get amirtham (the nectar of immortality). They used the Vasuki snake , Mount mandara , Kurma ( the Avatar of Lord Vishnu in the form of a turtle ) to churn the samudra manthan. While the churning (Samudra Manthan) happened, many things appeared such as Kamadhenu (wish granting cow) and Airavata (elephant).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bhajan Song</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/bhajan-song-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/bhajan-song-1/</guid>
      <description> The name of the songs are Akhanda Jyothi Jalao and Ek Baar Kshama Karo Sai. I sang these songs because it has a special place in my heart. The meaning of these songs are very heart warming and sweet. I learnt this song from the Centre Bhajan Singers.
 Bhajan - Akhanda Jyothi Jalao Your browser does not support the audio element..marginauto {margin: 10px auto 20px;display: block;}  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devotion Begins With Love</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/devotion_begins_with_love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/devotion_begins_with_love/</guid>
      <description>Both the above songs are dedicated to Swamiji to show my gratitude and love towards Him. The first song is known as &amp;ldquo;Ragupathi Ragava Raja Ram&amp;rdquo; which talks about Lord Rama and His selfless love to people around him. I have dedicated this song to Swamiji as I personally feel both of them have the same characteristics. I have read many stories about Swamiji and realized His selfless love towards His devotee around Him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lend a hand</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/lend-a-hand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/lend-a-hand/</guid>
      <description> Materials used:
 Rice Cardboard Spray Paint Hot Glue   Gallery 
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/love/</guid>
      <description>Start the day with love; Fill the day with love; Spend the day with love; End the day with love; This is the way to God. div.quote{font-style: italic; text-align:center;margin-top: auto;margin-bottom: auto;margin-left: 2em;margin-right: 2em;} Swami’s life is His message and His message is love. Love is the basis of human life.
If we see the world with love, it would be filled with positivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOVE = HAPPINESS</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/love-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/love-happiness/</guid>
      <description>Swami simplifies our understanding of the principle of love with a saying: &amp;ldquo;Love in thought is Sathya, Love in action is Dharma, Love in feeling is Shanti and Love in understanding is Ahimsa&amp;rdquo;. Love is the hidden current for all the human values. When we speak with love, it is Sathya. When work is saturated with love, it is Dharma. Life lived according to these values gives peace. Love coming from a peaceful heart brings bliss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love All Serve All</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/love-all-serve-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/love-all-serve-all/</guid>
      <description> With Swami&#39;s love and blessings, I do not fear this epidemic, as He is omnipresent and will be guiding me always
div.quote{font-style: italic; text-align:center;margin-top: auto;margin-bottom: auto;margin-left: 2em;margin-right: 2em;}  Gallery  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love for Swami</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/love-for-swami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/love-for-swami/</guid>
      <description>When I sing the glory of Swami, I will think of Him residing in my heart. I feel that He is listening to me singing happily. Humming His name also gives me pleasure. I hope Swami will enjoy listening to me singing this song. This is my way of showing my love towards Him. Sai Ram.
 Bhajan - Guru Baba Guru Baba Your browser does not support the audio element.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magical Gaze</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/magical-gaze/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/magical-gaze/</guid>
      <description> 
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Bhajan</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/my-bhajan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/my-bhajan/</guid>
      <description>I learned this song in my Balvikas.
The meaning of this song is: O mind, worship the Lotus Feet of your God and Supreme Teacher, Sai Baba who will take you safely across the ocean of Samsara. Victory to our Lord and supreme Teacher, Sai Nath! To chant and worship the divine names of Lord Shiva who dwells on the Arunachala mountain and Sai Baba whose form is OM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Painting with Calligraphy Art</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/calligraphy-painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/calligraphy-painting/</guid>
      <description> The background painting was inspired by pastel blue and pink aesthetics. A 95th birthday wish to Baba was lettered in calligraphic font. Some of Swami’s incredible quotes were written as well. Some details and decorations were added too.
 Gallery  
 References https://youtu.be/9RwKGTMFhbo
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signs &amp; Wonders Of Sathya Sai</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/signs-wonders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/signs-wonders/</guid>
      <description>Bhagwan Himself narrates a glimpse of amazing miracles towards mankind which is beyond one’s explanations. To comprehend Baba’s significant signs of wonders, we must delve faithfully to understand His glory and experience the element of divinity. The approach of love and affection that He showers upon all, is purely divine and magical. In a discourse on December 1976, He said that His manifestations were not to deceive and mislead the people but to attract, reconstruct, transform, and make them useful and serviceable for society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Life Story Of Baba</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/swami-life-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/swami-life-story/</guid>
      <description>I compiled an article about Swami&amp;rsquo;s Life story. I got the information to do the article in a few books and through internet search Google. This message is very important for me because so many people don&amp;rsquo;t know about the life story of Swami so I wanted everyone to know the story of Swami.
November 23, 1926, is a red-lettered day in the history of mankind. On that day was born in the obscure village of Puttaparthi, a charming baby boy in the Ratnakara family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why fear when I am here?</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/quote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/quote/</guid>
      <description>Bhagawan says, &amp;ldquo;Why fear when I am here&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;Fear&amp;rdquo; means fear of anything, imaginary or real, danger, disaster, or death. &amp;ldquo;When&amp;rdquo; means anytime, or all the time. &amp;ldquo;I am here&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;I am everywhere, I AM IN YOU and not outside you, not separate from you, wherever I am; in Prashanthi Nilayam, Brindavan or anywhere else.
In conclusion, we have no reason to fear as we have the Lord in our midst and have Him placed in our hearts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
