<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Group 3 on e-Magazine</title>
    <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/tags/group-3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Group 3 on e-Magazine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/tags/group-3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why fear when I am here?</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/quote/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/quote/</guid>
      <description>Bhagawan says, &amp;ldquo;Why fear when I am here&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;Fear&amp;rdquo; means fear of anything, imaginary or real, danger, disaster, or death. &amp;ldquo;When&amp;rdquo; means anytime, or all the time. &amp;ldquo;I am here&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;I am everywhere, I AM IN YOU and not outside you, not separate from you, wherever I am; in Prashanthi Nilayam, Brindavan or anywhere else.
In conclusion, we have no reason to fear as we have the Lord in our midst and have Him placed in our hearts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devotion Begins With Love</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/devotion_begins_with_love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/devotion_begins_with_love/</guid>
      <description>Both the above songs are dedicated to Swamiji to show my gratitude and love towards Him. The first song is known as &amp;ldquo;Ragupatthi Ragava Raja Ram&amp;rdquo; which talks about Lord Rama and His selfless love to people around him. I have dedicated this song to Swamiji as I personally feel both of them have the same characteristics. I have read many stories about Swamiji and realized His selfless love towards His devotee around Him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Painting with Calligraphy Art</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/calligraphy-painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/calligraphy-painting/</guid>
      <description> The background painting was inspired by pastel blue and pink aesthetics. A 95th birthday wish to Baba was lettered in calligraphic font. Some of Swami’s incredible quotes were written as well. Some details and decorations were added too.
 Gallery  
 References https://youtu.be/9RwKGTMFhbo
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Life Story Of Baba</title>
      <link>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/swami-life-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/swami-life-story/</guid>
      <description>I compiled an article about Swami&amp;rsquo;s Life story. I got the information to do the article in a few books and through internet search Google. This message is very important for me because so many people don&amp;rsquo;t know about the life story of Swami so I wanted everyone to know the story of Swami.
November 23, 1926, is a red-lettered day in the history of mankind. On that day was born in the obscure village of Puttaparthi, a charming baby boy in the Ratnakara family.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
