<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SSE / SSEHV Gurus on The Awakening</title>
    <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/tags/sse-/-ssehv-gurus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SSE / SSEHV Gurus on The Awakening</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/tags/sse-/-ssehv-gurus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Love Is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/mandala-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/mandala-art/</guid>
      <description> Mandala Art with a concept of love. Swami was my inspiration and the colours were from the idea of a colourful life. Colours describe joyfulness and happiness in one’s life. Mandala Art is something through which I have learnt to be patient and to manage my emotions.
Thank you
 Gallery 
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Best For Swami</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/my-best-for-swami/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/my-best-for-swami/</guid>
      <description>In every action we do, there are always two aspects to it – effort and result. The effort is always in our hands but more often than not the results aren’t. It is, however, in Swami’s hands. Therefore, it makes sense for us to focus all of our energy and time giving our best in the effort rather than focusing our time and energy on the outcome/results.
This thought then brings me to wonder how much effort is enough when we do something for Swami.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Baba Chose Parthi?</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/baba-and-parthi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/baba-and-parthi/</guid>
      <description>Below are some insights into different words/names related to Swami’s place in India and its significance to us as His devotees.
 Bharatha (India) → Bha + Ra+ Tha → feeling (bhava) – tune (raga) – rhythm (taala). Anantapur (city in Andhra Pradesh) → Ananta = infinite, pur = body.
 A devotee should have staunch faith like the Mountain Penukonda (mount/fort in Anantapur city) –&amp;gt; Penu means big, konda means mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
