<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ladies on The Awakening</title>
    <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/tags/ladies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ladies on The Awakening</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/tags/ladies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Divine Grace</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/divine-grace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/divine-grace/</guid>
      <description>Gita Samarpanam is a group born out of the vision and initiation of Aunty Jegadeva to recite the verses of Chapter 12 on Bhakti Yoga or Path of Devotion from the most revered holy book - the Bhagavad Gita. It is to be an offering to Bhagawan on Ladies Day for the year 2020.
I grabbed this opportunity to be a part of the sadhana not only as an offering but more importantly to learn to chant the verses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family is EVERYTHING</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/family-is-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/family-is-everything/</guid>
      <description>Amidst the widespread of Covid-19 we have all been lifted into another way of living. Our lives have been slowed down by an amazingly small organism with a huge amount of power. In March 2020, when the Movement Control Order was announced, there was sudden fear and panic everywhere.
Each day presented us with a new set of rules and changes that gave us a reason to pause. Schools closing, kids zoning out during endless Zoom classes, holiday plans cancelled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seek And You Will Find The Inner Peace You Crave</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/inner-peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/inner-peace/</guid>
      <description>When the coronavirus pandemic reached our shores and the Movement Control Order was announced, I was paradoxically elated. For I chose to look at the positive side, I decided that it was a great opportunity to take a breather from the hectic pace of life that I had become accustomed to. Rather then dwell on the negativity and worry unnecessarily over a virus that was restricting our way of life, I decided to make the most of the situation as best I could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service of Love</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/service-of-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/service-of-love/</guid>
      <description>Why doing service is important to you? How does the seva improve you as a person as a spiritual aspirant as a guru? Well, I don’t know that seva means performing without expecting a reward, or a result of an outcome. Little I know that Seva is a powerful tool to learn about myself, be it inner or outer. I was doing it for my grandmother, father, mom, siblings, and my school teachers continuously since I was a little girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gayatri Mantra</title>
      <link>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/gayatri_mantra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emagazine.ssbcbandarklang.org/p/gayatri_mantra/</guid>
      <description>Gayatri has 3 important aspects: Gayatri, Savitri and Saraswathi. What are these three? What do they signify?
The 1st Gayatri – Gaya means limbs of the body, the senses of the body. Gayatri means that which will take care of the effective functioning and well being of the body and senses. Gayatri means that the well-being of the body will be taken care of. Health is guaranteed. It is very important to have a sound mind in a sound body.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
